Destiny arrives all the same.
Avengers: Infinity War is a adventure, action, science
fiction film directed by Anthony Russo.
As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for
any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos.
A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of
unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality.
Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate
of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.
Tony Stark / Iron Man, played by Robert Downey Jr..
Steve Rogers / Captain America, played by Chris Evans.
Thor, played by Chris Hemsworth.
Thanos, played by Josh Brolin.
Bruce Banner / Hulk, played by Mark Ruffalo.
Natasha Romanoff / Black Widow, played by Scarlett Johansson.
Avengers: Infinity War is a 2018 American superhero film based on
the Marvel Comics superhero team the Avengers.
Produced by Marvel Studios and distributed by Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures, it is the sequel to The Avengers
(2012) and Avengers: Age of Ultron (2015), and the 19th film in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU).
Directed by Anthony and Joe Russo and written by Christopher Markus and Stephen McFeely, the film features an ensemble cast including Robert Downey Jr., Chris Hemsworth, Mark Ruffalo, Chris Evans, Scarlett Johansson, Benedict
Cumberbatch, Don Cheadle, Tom Holland, Chadwick Boseman, Paul Bettany, Elizabeth Olsen, Anthony Mackie, Sebastian Stan, Danai Gurira, Letitia Wright, Dave Bautista, Zoe Saldaña, Josh Brolin, and Chris Pratt.
In the film, the Avengers and the Guardians of the Galaxy attempt to stop Thanos from collecting the six
powerful Infinity Stones as part of his quest to kill half of all life in the universe.
The film was announced in October 2014 as Avengers: Infinity War – Part 1.
The Russo brothers came on board to direct in April 2015, and a month later, Markus and McFeely signed on to write the script for the film,
which draws inspiration from Jim Starlin's 1991 comic book The Infinity Gauntlet and Jonathan Hickman's 2013 comic book Infinity.
In 2016, Marvel shortened the title to Avengers: Infinity War.
Filming began in January 2017 at Pinewood Atlanta Studios in Fayette County, Georgia, with a large cast
consisting mostly of actors reprising their roles from previous MCU films, including Brolin as Thanos.
The production lasted until July 2017, shooting back-to-back
with a direct sequel, Avengers: Endgame (2019).
Additional filming took place in Scotland, the
Downtown Atlanta area, and New York City.
With an estimated budget of $325–400 million, the film is
one of the most expensive films ever made.
Avengers: Infinity War premiered at the Dolby Theatre in Hollywood, Los Angeles, on April 23, 2018,
and was released in the United States on April 27 as part of Phase Three of the MCU.
The film received positive reviews from critics, with praise for Brolin's performance and the Russo
brothers' direction, as well as the visual effects, action sequences, dark tone, and musical score.
It was a major box-office success, becoming the fourth film and the first superhero film to gross over $2 billion worldwide, breaking numerous box office records, and
becoming the highest-grossing film of 2018 and the fourth-highest-grossing film at the time of its release both worldwide and in the United States and Canada.
It received a nomination for Best Visual Effects at the 91st
Academy Awards, among numerous other accolades.
The sequel, Avengers: Endgame, was released in April 2019.
The film explores themes of sacrifice, magic, superhero, based on comic, space.
The tone is thought_provoking and mind_bending.